{"sid": "C73USRLQ0XM9_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 2011291, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 2011292, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 2017268]], "time_left_end": "295", "answered_time": 2017268, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "295", "question_time_start": 2017268, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 2023846]], "time_left_end": "288", "answered_time": 2023846, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "288", "question_time_start": 2023846, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 2039230]], "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 2039230, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 2039230, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 2046853]], "time_left_end": "265", "answered_time": 2046853, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "265", "question_time_start": 2046853, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 2060491]], "time_left_end": "251", "answered_time": 2060491, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "251", "question_time_start": 2060492, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 2067573]], "time_left_end": "244", "answered_time": 2067573, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "244", "question_time_start": 2067573, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 2072708]], "time_left_end": "239", "answered_time": 2072708, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "239", "question_time_start": 2072708, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 2078157]], "time_left_end": "234", "answered_time": 2078157, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "234", "question_time_start": 2078157, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 2087343]], "time_left_end": "224", "answered_time": 2087343, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "224", "question_time_start": 2087344, "question": "58+39", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 2093723]], "time_left_end": "218", "answered_time": 2093723, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 2093723, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "218", "question_time_start": 2093723, "question": "3+94+33", "correct_answer": 130, "events": [["submit", 2103014]], "time_left_end": "209", "answered_time": 2103014, "user_answer": "130", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "209", "question_time_start": 2103014, "question": "74+53", "correct_answer": 127, "events": [["submit", 2106809]], "time_left_end": "205", "answered_time": 2106809, "user_answer": "127", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "205", "question_time_start": 2106810, "question": "3+57+86", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["submit", 2110851]], "time_left_end": "201", "answered_time": 2110851, "user_answer": "146", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "201", "question_time_start": 2110851, "question": "99+63+57+23", "correct_answer": 242, "events": [["calc_9", 2121743], ["calc_9", 2121910], ["calc_+", 2122712], ["calc_1", 2123395], ["calc_4", 2123883], ["calc_3", 2124701], ["calc_=", 2125446], ["submit", 2130820]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 2130820, "user_answer": "242", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 2130820, "question": "9+98+96", "correct_answer": 203, "events": [["submit", 2153324]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 2153324, "user_answer": "201", "user_correct": "False", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 2153324, "question": "7+9+8+44", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 2163221]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 2163221, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 2163222, "question": "94+173", "correct_answer": 267, "events": [["submit", 2171107]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 2171107, "user_answer": "267", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 2171107, "question": "8+6+4+99", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 2177023]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 2177023, "user_answer": "117", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 2177023, "question": "37+199", "correct_answer": 236, "events": [["submit", 2182121]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 2182121, "user_answer": "236", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 2182121, "question": "67+74", "correct_answer": 141, "events": [["submit", 2186963]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 2186963, "user_answer": "143", "user_correct": "False", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 2186963, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 2186963, "question": "6+87+69", "correct_answer": 162, "events": [["calc_9", 2207026], ["calc_3", 2207896], ["calc_+", 2209214], ["calc_6", 2209829], ["calc_9", 2210428], ["calc_=", 2211215], ["submit", 2219264]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 2219264, "user_answer": "162", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 2219264, "question": "8+23+34", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 2228772]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 2228772, "user_answer": "65", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 2228772, "question": "78+764", "correct_answer": 842, "events": [["submit", 2238155]], "time_left_end": "74", "answered_time": 2238155, "user_answer": "842", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "74", "question_time_start": 2238155, "question": "94+87", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 2244299]], "time_left_end": "67", "answered_time": 2244299, "user_answer": "181", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "67", "question_time_start": 2244300, "question": "4+4+8+68", "correct_answer": 84, "events": [["submit", 2253100]], "time_left_end": "59", "answered_time": 2253100, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "False", "score": "19"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "59", "question_time_start": 2253100, "question": "57+26+88+33", "correct_answer": 204, "events": [["calc_9", 2267441], ["calc_0", 2268123], ["calc_+", 2268845], ["calc_2", 2269469], ["calc_6", 2270042], ["calc_+", 2270658], ["calc_8", 2271358], ["calc_8", 2272419], ["calc_=", 2273239], ["submit", 2278275]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "34", "answered_time": 2278275, "user_answer": "204", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "34", "question_time_start": 2278275, "question": "76+547", "correct_answer": 623, "events": [["submit", 2287860]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 2287860, "user_answer": "623", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 2287860, "question": "4+16+34", "correct_answer": 54, "events": [["submit", 2291213]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 2291213, "user_answer": "54", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 2291213, "question": "4+6+7+69", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 2299362]], "time_left_end": "12", "answered_time": 2299362, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "12", "question_time_start": 2299362, "question": "29+94", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 2306243]], "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 2306243, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 2306244, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 2306244, "question": "4+98+16", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 2310580]], "time_left_end": "1", "answered_time": 2310580, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "1", "question_time_start": 2310581, "question": "9+8+6+14", "correct_answer": 37, "events": []}}}}}